I think we can see them , guys.
Drop down.
Yeah, we can see them from down here.
Break the Gloo Wall.
Wait, do we have a good angle from down here?
Three of them are weak, guys.
Break it, we can break it from here.
Knocked one, confirm him.
Those guys are fighting each other.
Yo, let's go now, guys.
Go right.
Rotate right.
Rotate right, come to me.
Sniper behind the rock
Two left.
Sniper bendind the rock. Get ready for a 4v4.
Sniper is in front of me, ABCD.
Catch him, Catch him.
Push him, MinkCuog goooo
Push him now.
Go on MinkCuog.
Push him, push!
Go for Oscar.
Wait.
Wait, he's backing up.
He's weak, he's weak.
Oscar .
Okay, okay, there's still one on the other side.
I used Oscar.
They're fighting on the other side.
Let's go, ABCD!
Need an M590? Come to me, I'll give you one.
Take it slow.
One is weak.
I am coming
Only three left.
Already done
There are M590s everywhere, bro.
Okay, I'll take the M590. Give me a sec.
Morse is right next to us.
Clear, only two left.
Let's go, guys!
Let's fight.
Have UAV heal, let's push him now.
Here is UAV heal
Anyone drive the car? Let's go with car
Wait, wait.
Nice, nice.
100 HP.
Morse there.
Another 100 HP.
One is weak.
Nice!
Fall back right.
They confimed me, two of them are inside Gloo Wall.
That's right, ABCD.
They're stacked on top of each other.
It's done.
Nice
Only one left.
Break Gloo Wall.
He's weak.
Let's gooooo!
We're playing so damn well, guys!